いただきまーす
美味しい
うん　ママのカレー最高
そう　リンゴは本当にカレーが好きなのね
Let's eat!
うん　あたしカレー大好き
Is it tasty?
リンゴ
Yeah! Your curry is the best, Mom!
くすぐったい
そんなにゲットしたら食べられねよ
Is it?
You must really love curry.
ママ　どうしたの
Yeah, I love curry!
ううん　なんでもない
ただママ嬉しくて
Ringo...
That tickles!
変なの
I can't eat with you squeezing me like that!
はは　狡いぞ
ママはリンゴを独り占めするつもりだな
What's wrong, Mommy?
よし　パパもぎゅっとしちゃうぞ
Nothing. I'm just really happy.
パパ
You're acting strange!
リンゴはパパとママの大切な大切な宝ものだ
No fair! Mom's trying to keep you all for herself!
これからもずっとこうして家族一緒でいいよな
Then, Daddy will give you a big hug too!
うん　リンゴ　パパもママもカレーも大好き
Daddy!
You're our precious treasure, Ringo.
大切な人と食べるカレーは幸せな味がする
We'll be a family together like this, forever.
Yeah, Ringo loves daddy and mommy and curry!
くるくる回る
Curry eaten with people you love tastes like happiness.
君の瞳探して回る
駅のホーム
響くファンファーレ
<< kurukuru mawaru kimi no hitomi >>
<< Round and round, your eyes wander around >>
ガラガラ音を立てる街
<< sagashite mawaru eki no home >>
<< Searching around the station's platforms >>
とりあえず耳を貸してみたの
<< hibiku fanfare >>
<< The sound of fanfare from afar >>
もうすぐ消えるはずの世界に
<< garagara oto wo tateru machi >>
<< The clamorous city making noise >>
<< toriaezu mimi wo kashite ita no >>
<< I tried to keep an ear out for all this >>
<< mousugu kieru hazu no sekai ni >>
<< In a world that's about to end >>
ごめんね
もう二度と会えないようなそんな気がして
<< gomen ne >>
<< I'm sorry >>
運命が笑う
<< mou nido to aenai youna sonna ki ga shite >>
<< I just had a feeling I would never see you again >>
臨界点突破してんだ
限界なら既に去って
<< unmei ga warau >>
<< Fate is laughing at us >>
絶対的支配だって
崩壊
<< rinkaiten toppa shiten da >>
<< I'm already past the point of no return >>
終末理論は机上の空論でしかないって
<< genkai nara sude ni satte >>
<< Far over my limit >>
<< zettaiteki shihai datte >>
<< Even your absolute control has >>
ゼロとイチの世界線の果てから
<< houkai >>
<< Crumbled >>
<< shuumatsu riron wa kijou no kuuron shika naitte >>
<< "The end of the world is nothing but a hypothesis" >>
叫ぶよ
<< 0 to 1 no sekaisen no hate kara sakebu yo >>
<< Is what I'm crying out from other side of the binary world line >>
もうすぐ君が会いにくるような気がして
僕は目を閉じるよ
<< mou sugu kimi ga ai ni kuru you na ki ga shite >>
<< I have a feeling you'll come see me soon >>
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听 xHunter
翻译：英英 校对：凌可乐
时间轴：绯桜闲   压制：笑眯咪
<< boku wa me wo tojiru yo >>
<< So I will be waiting with my eyes closed >>
Good.
よし　出来た
It's done!
Ringo
Keiju
Chowtime!
いただきまーす
Oh, no! I'm going to be late!
嫌だ　もうこんな時間
I have an important meeting tonight,
ママ今日は大事な会議があるから
so eat dinner without me.
夜は先に食べて頂戴ね
It's the 20th, Mom.
ママ　今日は二十日だよ
I know.
うん　分かってる
I'll eat curry out tonight.
ママは外でカレー食べてくるから
Can you eat out tonight with your friends?
悪いけど　リンゴもお友達と外で食べてくれる
Mom!
ママ
もう　何
What?
You forgot a curler.
カーラーついてる
Oh, no!
あら　嫌だ
もう
The 20th of every month is Curry Day.
毎月二十日はカレーの日
Phone
Burnables
Curry Day
Meeting
That's our family rule.
それが我が家のルールだ
But today is an exception.
でも今日は特別
Because it's the day he will eat my curry for the very first time.
だって　あたしが作ったカレーを初めて彼に食べてもらう日だから
I have to make a special curry filled with love!
愛を込めた特製カレーを作らなきゃ
I'll grind the carrots that he hates,
彼の嫌いな人参は擦り落として
and add plenty of potatoes that he loves!
大好きなジャガイモはたっぷりと
And the secret flavor is apple jam.
そして秘密な隠し味はリンゴのジャム
It may not look pretty,
見た目はちょっと悪いけど
そんなことは気にしない
but it doesn't matter.
I'm sure it'll make him happy!
きっと喜んでくれるはず
Because he and I are bounded by fate!
だって　彼とあたしは運命で繋がれているのだから
Survival Strategy!
生存戦略
Welcome to Rock'n Roll Night
Welcome to Rock'n Roll Fight
I'm just a Rock'n Roll Man
I'm just a Rock'n Roll MAN
We're just a Rock'n Roll BAND
俺たちは道なりに　歩き続けてきた
We've been running down this road
標識だらけの道を飛ばし続けていく
Racing through a path full of signs
幾つもの町を抜け　歌い続けてきた
We crossed countless towns, spreading our song
腑抜け野郎共を煽り続けていく
Continuing to torment these cowardly fools
長い長い冬が溶けても風が吹く
The wind blows even after the lengthy winter
今も今も激しく風が吹く
Still storming down the road
Imagine!
Listen, you lowlifes who will never amount to anything.
きっと何物にも成れないお前たちに告げる
What, what, what?!
Obtain the Penguin Drum.
ピングドラムを手に入れるのだ
Quit using these grand-scale
illusions to mess with us, Himari!
こんな大掛かりなイリュージョンで悪戯するのはもうやめようひまり
Huh?
I mean, this "Survival Strategy" and "Penguin Drum" business is absurd!
だって　生存戦略とかピングドラムとか馬鹿見えてるよ
I know you get bored when you're home alone,
一人きりで家に居るのが辛いからせ　こんなイリュージョンで遊んでたら
but how are you going to be normal again if you keep playing with these illusions?!
社会復帰出来なくなっちゃうよ
Cut it out already, Himari.
もう　終りにしよう　ひまり
So, you fools still don't believe in my existence?
つまり　貴様らまだわらわの存在を信じられぬと申すか
It is an impressive illusion, though.
よく出来たイリュージョンだけどな
フー　下等生物にも猜疑心はあるというわけか
I see. So even lower life forms are capable of suspicion.
Then I shall make you believe.
ならば　信じさせてやろう
In the most effective manner.
これ以上ないという方法でな
M
i
t
s
u
e
M
i
l
k
I shall drink this now.
いまより　これを飲む
貴様らの妹は牛乳が飲めなかったはずだな
Your sister couldn't drink milk, if I remember correctly.
That's correct...
そうですけど
Watch this, then.
いいか　よく見ろ　　どうだ
Take this!
Do you believe now?
どうだ　これで信じたか
Burp.
That's amazing, Himari!
凄いじゃないか　ひまり
僕たちに内緒で練習して来たんだね
You practiced drinking milk without telling us!
I don't have to worry about your calcium intake now.
これでカルシウムは大丈夫だな
Okay, end the illusion now!
マー　イリュージョン終わり終わり
You don't believe me?
信じないのか
Nope.
うん
Then you leave me no choice.
ならば致し方ない
You shall witness the nightmare once more, you imbeciles.
貴様らもう一度あの悪夢を見るがよい
H-Himari?
ひまり
Himari!
She's... not breathing...
息してない
T-The hat really was alive!
やっぱり帽子は生きてるんだ
She'll die without the hat!
帽子がないとひまりが死んちゃうんだ
Do you see where you stand now?
己の立場が理解出来たか
N-No way...
そ　そんな
Forcing us to do things by blackmailing us like that...
なんかそんなやり方で僕たちを脅かして無理強い売って酷くねねね
is unfair!
Let's initiate the Survival Strategy.
生存戦略　しましょうか
行っちゃたね
She left.
ああ
Yeah.
よし　留守のようだな
Good, looks like nobody's home.
B-Bro, that's...
兄貴　それ
悔しいが
I hate to admit it, but the hat's right.
あいつの言う通りだ
No matter how risky it is,
例えどんなにやばいことだろうと
ひまりの命を救えるのなら
we'll have to do anything we can to save Himari.
俺たちはやるしかないんだ
The only question is, how far will we be willing to go?
後は何処までの覚悟俺たちがするかというだけだ
For Himari.
ひまりのために
For Himari!
アア　何疊くらいあるんだろう
I wonder what the square footage is.
Come on, let's get this over with.
ほら　さっさと片づけるぞ
We're really starting to look like thieves.
なんか　本当に泥棒っぽいよね
If the Penguin Drum really is here, then that's what we'll be.
ここにピングドラムがあれば　そうなるだろうな
Phone
Burnables
Curry Day
Meeting
"Curry Day"?
カレーの日
Plums
I wonder what it is.
何だろう
Plums
It's today.
今日じゃなんだ
Hey, do you wanna hear more
about that hottie from the train?
ねね
この間のイケメン君の続報聞きたい
What is it? Tell me!
なにそれ　聞きたい　聞きたい
According to a friend at cram school,
塾の友達に聞いたんだけど
he's Asami Kuho's ex-boyfriend!
あの子は久宝阿佐美の元彼なんだって
Asami Kuho?
久宝阿佐美
What, you don't know?
嫌だ　知らないの
She's in that magazine called Sixteen...
シックスティーンって言う雑誌の
The model?
あのモデルの
That's amazing!
ええ　凄くない
Yeah, but this is the juicy part:
でもこっからがいいんだわ
He dumped Asami Kuho like she was no big deal!
彼　久宝阿佐美のこと超あっさりふっちゃたんだって
"Girls who are nothing but a pretty face are no fun."
顔だけの女は詰まらね
Potatoes,
ジャガイモ　人参　セロリ 　豚肉
carrots,
That's kind of hot!
celery, and
それちょっとカッコいいかも
pork.
Ringo's
We seriously shouldn't go in there!
やっばここはまずいよ
Ringo's
If the Penguin Drum is her personal belonging,
ピングドラムがあの女の私物なら
Ringo's
then it's most likely in here.
ここにある確率が一番高いだろう
But...
でも　女の子の部屋に　可哀相じゃないか
It's a girl's private room.
I feel bad for her!
You feel bad?
可哀相
She's a total freak who sneaked under Tabuki's house,
あいつは多蕗地の床したに入り込んで
盗聴までしていやがった
and even bugged his room!
完全の変態　ストーカー女だぞ
Plums
A stalker girl.
There's nothing to feel bad about!
可哀相もくそもあるか
だけど
But...
If you can't, then I will.
お前ができないなら
俺がやる
マー　いいさ
Oh, well.
Save your innocence for Himari.
お前の良心って奴はひまりのためにとっておけ
Bro-
Plums
Penguin Curry
This one!
これ
Hey, Bro.
ねね　兄貴
うん
What exactly is the Penguin Drum anyway?
ピングドラムって何なんだろうね
Will we really find it by aimlessly searching for it?
こうして　当てもなく探し回って　見つかるものなのかな
Who knows?
さーな
Stop talking and start searching!
しゃべてないで　手を動かせ
まだ台所は未調査だ
We still haven't searched the kitchen.
そういうことじゃなくて
That's not what I mean...
I know what you're trying to say.
ああ　分かってるよ
お前はこういう汚れ仕事がしたくないんだろう
You don't want to get your hands dirty like this.
これも外れか
Nothing here either.
嫌なら　手を出さなくてもいい
You don't have to help if you don't want to.
But then, the hero who finds the Penguin Drum and saves Himari will be me.
ただし　ピングドラムを見つけてひまりを救うのはこの俺ってことになるけどな
Fine, I'll do it.
分かったよ　やればいいんでしょ　やれば
You happy?
I'm home!
ただいまー
Curry, curry.
カレー　カレー
It's super-awesome Curry Day!
今日は楽しいカレーの日
What do we do?
どうしよう
シー　いい機会だ
Shh, it's a good opportunity.
She might let her guard down, and let something slip.
あの女一人だと安心して
何か襤褸を出すかもしれない
I think the first food cooked by humans may have been curry.
人類の歴史の中で
人が初めて作った料理はカレーだったんじゃないかと思う
And it must have been made by a girl for the person she loves.
それに作ったのはきっと女の子
大好きな人に食べてもらうために
So she could see him smile at how delicious it is.
美味しいねって微笑んでもらうために
Humans started fires, made tools and gathered ingredients.
火を起し
道具を作り
材料を用意して
That's why curry has the taste of happiness.
だからカレーは幸せな味がする
Seasoning the meat in ground apple so it doesn't get hard––that's our family's secret recipe.
煮こんでも硬くならないように
擦り寄ろしたリンゴでお肉を漬け込むのが我が家の秘伝
Sauté the roux separately with cumin,
ルートは別に　くみにもよく炒めたら
then add the other ingredients.
他の具材を入れてやる
I love the boiling sound.
お鍋の煮える音が好き
Those whispers of the ingredients as they try to get tastier in order to make him happy.
美味しくなろう　あの人を喜ばせてあげようってあげまし合う具材たちの囁き
Just like a mother whispering to her baby between lullabies.
丁度子守歌合間に
御母さんが赤ちゃんに語りかけるように
Whispering, "I love you, let's be together forever."
大好き　いつまでもずっとに一緒にいようねって
That's why you have to eat curry with the person you love, who you want to be together with forever.
だから　カレーは大好きな人とずっとずっと傍に居たいって思える人と食べなきゃいけない
That's the rule.
それがルール
March 20th, 2006 - Oginome Family Apartment - Ringo Oginome 11 years old
* That Curry Day, Tabuki seemed to be glittering, our fate has been written in stone since that day
Curry Day
Don't hold back. Eat as much as you want!
遠慮せず　沢山食べていて頂戴ね
I will, thank you.
はい　ありがとうございます
So, you're finally graduating from high school, Keiju?
桂樹君も高校卒業か
Time sure flies!
月日の経つのは早いものね
It tastes great, as usual!
いつも美味しいですね
Well, thank you.
マア　ありがとう
It's actually our secret family recipe!
実は我が家の秘伝があるのよ
Right, Ringo?
ね　リンゴ
Yes, that's why curry must...
そう　だから　カレーは
Good, it's done!
よし　出来た
いいな　カレーか
Smell great... curry...
It's tasty!
美味しい
Idiot!
馬鹿　腹の虫自分でコントロールしろう
Make your stomach shut up!
That's not even possible!
無茶な
わ　こっち来るよ
She's coming!
The project has advanced to the next stage.
これでまた一歩プロジェクトが進行したわ
There's nothing to worry about.
心配しなくても大丈夫全ては運命の通りに進んでいる
Everything is happening as written by fate.
Fate?
運命
Hey, is it just me, or does it smell?
なー　先から何か匂うんかね
Smell?
匂う
Uh, something foreign.
ああ　何と言うか　外国っぽい
This smell is...
この匂いはカレーですか
Is it curry?
Physicurry
Odor
But why does it smell like that in a subway car?
でも　どうして地下鉄で
Where is she trying to take that curry, anyway?
それにしても　カレー何か作って何処に持って行くつもりなんだろう
It may not be an ordinary curry.
ただのカレーじゃないかもしれないぞ
For example, the mixture of the spice could be a code of sorts.
例えば　スパイスの配合が何かの暗号になってるとか
Or perhaps that curry itself may be the Penguin Drum.
或いは　あのカレーそのものがピングドラムである可能性もすっと切てない
Are you sure?
そうかな
It just looks like an ordinary pot of curry to me.
どう見ても普通のカレーにしか見えないけどな
Hey, Bro, is this the road to...
ね　兄貴　もしかして　この道
Yeah, she's heading toward Tabuki's home.
ああ　あの女
目的は多蕗家だ
Yes?
はい
Oh, Ringo!
あれ　リンゴちゃん
Welcome.
いらっしゃい
Uh, um...
あの　これ
Take this!
It's Curry Day today,
今日はカレーの日だから　一緒に食べようと思って
so I thought we could eat together...
It's tasty!
美味しい　お料理上手なんだね　きっといいお嫁さんになるな
You're a great cook!
You'll definitely become an excellent wife!
N-No way...
そんな　カレーぐらい
It's just curry...
ああ　あの　今度の野鳥の観察会　あたしお弁当持っていきます
I'll make something for the birdwatching group next time.
Really? I can't wait!
本当　それりゃ楽しみだな
Do you really have time, though? You must be busy with cram school.
でも　いいの
塾もあるし　大変じゃない
No, not at all!
全然
I'll do anything for you, Tabuki!
あたし多蕗さんのためなら　何だって
Ringo...
リンゴちゃん
Tabuki...
多蕗さん
御帰り　多蕗君
Welcome back, Tabuki!
Huh?
あら
That's a surprise. Tabuki actually has his own woman.
あの多蕗に女がいるとは　意外だったな
The stalker ran into the girlfriend!
ストーカーと本命の彼女鉢合わせだ
A showdown, huh?
修羅場か
Here you go.
はい　どうぞ
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
This sucks.
災厄
You're a student from Tabuki's school, right?
多蕗君の学校の生徒さんよね
I'm sorry, but he's not back yet.
御免なさいね　まだ彼帰ってきてないのよ
Oh, I see.
そうなんですか
I'm making dinner right now.
ああ　今お夕飯を作っていてね
It's curry.
カレーなんだけど　よかったら　一緒にいかが
Why don't you join us?
Curry?
カレー
He told me it's Curry Day today.
そう　今日はカレーの日だらかって彼が
Isn't he strange? He's like a child.
変よね　子供みたい
There's no way you can understand.
あなたなんかに分かるはずない
The fate that binds Tabuki and me...
私と多蕗さんの運命は
It must be him this time.
今度こそきっと多蕗君ね
Welcome home.
お帰りなさい
ただいま
I'm finally back.
What should I do, the plan is ruined!
どうしよう
これじゃ計画が台無しに
Tabuki has to eat my curry today.
今日多蕗さんが食べるのは私のカレー
I can't let this happen... I have to do it.
だめよ　やらなきゃ
It's Curry Day today!
今日はカレーの日
うちは男子高だけど
...I work at an all-boy's school.
This is the yogurt you asked for.
ア　これ頼まれてたヨーグルト
I hope I got the right one.
これでよかったかな
Now's the chance, Ringo!
いまよ　リンゴ
Muster up the courage!
勇気を出して
Oh, okay. This is the one I needed.
ああ　これで大丈夫よ
Thanks.
ありがとう
Thank you, Tabuki.
ありがとう　多蕗君
Don't mention it.
いいよ　いいよ
Sorry to keep you wai-
御免ね　お待たせしちゃっ
Huh?
あら
Fabulous Max!
Fabulous mas
In any case, it went as it was fated.
とにかく運命の通りに渡ったんだから
Tabuki is eating my curry.
多蕗さんが食べるのは私のカレー
So, it's all fine.
だから　大丈夫
That woman is nothing compared to our bond.
あんな女なんて　私たちの絆に比べたら
Yes, everything is going according to the plan.
そう　全ては計画通り順調
Not a single problem...
なんの問題も
この泥棒猫
You thieving cat!
Geez, they're hopeless!
もう　信じられない
My brothers skipped school again.
お兄ちゃんたちまた学校サボったらしいわよ
They're sentenced to no dinner tonight!
今日は二人ども御飯抜きの刑かな
Threetie!
三ちゃん
No, don't eat off the ground!
やません　拾いぐみは
Stop, kitty!
猫さんもだめ　仲よくしなきゃ
You two should play nice!
W-Watch out!
危ない
Uh... I'm sorry.
あのう　御免なさい
Himari must be mad.
ひまり　怒ってるよね
I bet she is.
だろうな
We failed at tailing Oginome Ringo,
荻野目リンゴの尾行には失敗するし
found out nothing about the Penguin Drum,
ピングドラムの手掛かりもなし
and to top it off we'll be scolded by Himari!
そのうえ　ひまりに怒られるか
Bro?
兄貴
Yeah...
You lose if you're late. Rock, paper, scissors!
出さないじゃ負けよ　ジャンゲンボン
We're home...
ただいま
You're late!
遅い
Sorry, Himari!
御免ひまり
You're getting an earful tonight...
今日こそ大目玉と言いたいところだけど
is what I was about to say, but I'll make an exception.
特別に許してあげる
Right, Ringo?
ね　リンゴちゃん
My brothers are home.
お兄ちゃんたち帰ってきたよ
Ringo Oginome. We became friends earlier.
荻野目リンゴさん
さっきお友達になったんだ
もういいかな　リンゴちゃん
Is it done now, Ringo?
うん　そうだね
Yeah, I think so.
ねー　これで何がどうなっちゃってるわけ
Hey...
What exactly is going on here?
Don't ask me!
俺に聞くな
Thanks for waiting!
お待たせ
You must be hungry.
お腹空いたでしょ
We're having the Special Honey Apple Curry tonight!
今日は特製リンゴ蜂水カレーです
The meat is so tender in this curry, it's tasty!
このカレー　お肉も柔らかくて美味しい
Super Strong
Adhesive
Mouse Trap
Ringo, you're a great cook.
リンゴちゃんお料理上手なんだね
Not really, I can only make curry.
うんー　出来るのはカレーだけ
Because I learned it from my mom when I was little.
昔お母さんに教わたから
That must be nice. Your mom taught you?
いいな　御母さんが教えてくてたんだ
I've been craving curry all day.
今日はなんだかずっとカレーが食べたかったんだ
ひまり　どうして　分かったの
How did you know, Himari?
それりゃ家族だもの
We're family, after all!
Right, Ringo?
ねね　リンゴちゃん
Right...
うん　ひまりちゃんは幸せだね
You must be happy, Himari.
I mean, you're eating curry with people you love.
だって　大切な人とカレーを食べてる
That's how you're supposed to eat curry.
カレーはそうして食べるものだもの
Ringo...
リンゴちゃん
I'm happy I got to eat curry with you, Ringo.
ねー　私はリンゴちゃんとカレーが食べられて嬉しいよ
Because you're a friend I love!
だって　大切なお友達だし
It's been so long since we've had company.
家にお客様が来るなんて本当久しぶりだもん
Right, Sho?
ねね　晶ちゃん　　うん　そうだね
Yeah, you're right.
So, you're welcome here anytime!
だから　大歓迎
Come here again if you don't have anyone to eat with.
また一人御飯の時は家においてよ
Let's eat together.
一緒に食べよう
Okay, thanks.
うん　ありがとう
By the way, Oginome.
ところで　荻野目さん
Did you have an important task...
今日は何か大切な用事が　計画があったんじゃないんですか
A plan for today?
That's too straightforward, bro!
兄貴　いきなり
No problem.
大丈夫
It didn't go as planned,
少し予定が狂ったけど
but today worked out fine.
今日はもう大丈夫
Since everything went as was written.
ちゃんと書いてある通りになっているから
そう　それが一番大切なこと
Yes... that's the most important thing.
記されて運命を実行することが私の生まれてきた理由
To execute the fate already written down.
That's my reason for existence.
It's an important mission of mine.
大事なミッションだもの
Dear Mom.
ママへ
今夜は友達とカレーを食べました
I had curry with friends tonight.
It's been a while since I ate curry with others.
他の人とカレーを食べるのは久しぶり
But it tastes the best with family...
でもやっぱり家族
Dear Mom, I had curry with friends
tonight. It's been a while since I ate
curry with others.
But it tastes the
Dear Mom, I had curry with friends
tonight. It's been a while since I ate
curry with others.
But it tastes the
Dear Mom, I had curry with friends
tonight. It's been a while since I ate
curry with others.
But it tastes the
Dear Mom, I had curry with friends
tonight. It's been a while since I ate
curry with others.
But it tastes the
Curry definitely tastes the best at home.
我が家で食べるカレーが一番美味しいです
I went to Tabuki's home and ate my homemade curry together. Tabuki smiled like a child. I saw a cat that made an evil look on the way home. It was scary.
Destiny.
destiny
Then Devour Me Currageously
subete ga moshi kimerarete tara
If everything was written in stone
全てがもし
決められてたら
bokura wa doushite mogaku no darou
Why have we been resisting our fate?
僕らはどうして
もがくのだろう
それは君じゃない
sore wa kimi ja nai
It's not you
kimi no sei ja nai
It's not your fault
君のせいじゃない
悲しみはもう沢山なんだ
kanashimi wa mou takusan nanda
I've had enough misery
dakara sou ja nai
You're mistaken
だからそうじゃない
今のままじゃない
ima no mama ja nai
Fate can be changed
うまく伝えきれないけど
umaku tsutaekirenai kedo
I can't explain it, but
DEAR MY FUTURE
Dear my future
Dear your future
DEAR YOUR FUTURE
Does that mean her fate is written here?
これに彼女の運命が記されてるってこと
Then what we're trying to do is...
だとしたら
今からやろうとしていることは
Lily Hoshino